Thanks to the hard work of interns and contributors
感谢各位实习生和贡献者的辛苦工作
GNOME announce the version 3.18
GNOME 正式发布 3.18 版本
In this release GNOME improves the general user experience for users and new developers alike
在这个版本中，GNOME 为普通用户和新开发者提升了用户体验
If you computer has a light sensor
如果你的电脑有光线传感器
GNOME can now use it automatically adjust the brightness of your screen
GNOME 现在可以使用它自动来调节你的屏幕的亮度
the touchscreen experience has also improved when selecting and modifying text
触摸屏提升了选择和修改文本的体验
"Files" has received a lot of attention this cycle
这个版本的“文件管理器”也有了大量改变
there's a new view in the sidebar
侧边栏有了新的视图风格
so remote and internal locations are collected in one place for your convenience
远程和内部位置放在一起以便操作
Progress is now shown in the header bar when files are being copy
当文件复制的时候顶部也会显示进度条
There are many other improvements
还有很多其他改进
inlcuding  a more polished search function,
包括了更细腻的搜索体验、
Google Drive integration
集成了 Google Drive
and better file management.
以及更好的文件管理。
"Software" has become the first suport updating device firmware
“软件”首先支持设备固件的更新
use new Linux Vendor firmware service
通过新的 Linux 厂商固件服务程序。
The service allows vendors to submit firmware
这个服务支持厂家提交固件
and GNOME Software allow allow you to install it with the click of a button
GNOME 软件程序将允许你一键安装固件
Further more, the GNOME community has improved a large variety of Apps.
同时，GNOME 社区也完善了大量应用程序，
including "Calendar"
包括"日历”
which now comes with a management dialog to help you manage your calendars.
现在有了一个管理对话框来帮助你管理日历。
Polari
Polari (IRC 客户端)
with a better initially user experience.
有了更好的初始化用户体验。
GNOME Documents
GNOME 文档
which is supporting a revamped user interface for organizing your documents.
现在支持改变用户界面以更好的组织文档
And Evince
还有 Evince (pdf 文件阅读器)
which annotation and video support has improved.
提升了注解和对视频的支持。
GNOME 3.18 comes with a preview of the GNOME To Do
GNOME 3.18 还包括了预览版的 GNOME To Do
a personal task manager helping you keep track of the tasks ahead of time.
一款个人任务管理工具，帮助你跟踪任务和规划时间
GNOME development tools have also improved in this cycles
这个版本对 GNOME 的开发工具也有了提升
Builder for example
例如 Builder (GNOME 集成开发环境)
now has a source code minimap
现在有了查看源代码的快捷键minimap
a shortcut overview
一个快捷键预览
and an auto completion for Python
以及 Python 语言的自动完成功能
the Human Interface Guidelines have been restructured
用户界面规则也重新规划了
and including new usage pattern.
增加了新的使用模式。
GNOME Logs user interface now goes better overview
GNOME Logs 的用户界面有了更好的预览
I can show you logs from the last five boots.
可以显示最后 5 次启动的日志。
Boxes has improved interface
Boxes 也改进了界面
with the new list view
有了新的列表视图
for users with a lot of virtual machines.
方便有大量虚拟机的用户。
Finally GTK+ has received new typographic features
最后，GTK+ 有了新的字体特性
A new GNOME relase is available for you
你现在可以获得新版 GNOME
as a live image to try now.
它是一个 live 版的镜像
（视频中的地址有误，可访问上一级目录查看）
Many distributions will also ship  GNOME 3.18 in the near future.
很多发行版都会在未来搭载 GNOME 3.18。
GNOME is a friendly community making free software for everyone.
GNOME 是一个为每个人构建自由软件的友好社区。
Excited?
心动了？
join us in making the perfect desktop environment!
加入我们让 GNOME 成为完美的桌面环境！